https://funkluscious.com/privacy-policy/

Free Shipping on All Orders Over $75!
About
Customer Service
Privacy Policy
Terms
Funk Luscious Couture respects your privacy. We do not like our personal information shared so your information is safe with us. The information collected on this site is used to process orders and provide you, our customer, with the best possible products, website, and customer service. Funk Luscious Couture’s website is not intended for minors. Funk Luscious Couture does not knowingly solicit or collect personal information from minors. If a minor chooses to use this website it must be done under adult supervision.
Personal Information
In order to subscribe to our email notifications we must have your email address. If you place an order, we require your address, phone and credit card information. We will not disclose this information to any third party except for your shipping carrier. Any non-personal information we collect will be used to better your shopping experience and create a more user friendly website.
Who sees your information?
The only people who have access to our order database are employees who process your orders. We do not distribute our client lists to anyone. We treat your information as if it was our own. Mum’s the word here!
Security:
Funk Luscious Couture uses a secure server in order to protect your information.
Yum, Cookies, and how do we use them?
Funk Luscious Couture does use browser Cookies. This enables us to better track our customers and offer an enhanced shopping experience. We will never use cookies to gain access to information that is unrelated to our site or services. Cookies identify the user’s computer, not the user’s personal information. In addition, they are used to maintain items put into your shopping bag.
Need to make account changes?
You can make changes to your funk luscious account information by clicking on the My Account tab on the FLC home page. If at anytime you wish to cancel your account you can email customerservice@funkluscious.com. We will remove your personal information from our confidential customer database.
By using this website you are consenting to the collection and use of your private information as described in the Privacy Policy. If Funk Luscious Couture modifies our privacy policy in any way we will post the new information on this page. All changes will become effective immediately following the posting. If at anytime and for any reason you choose to not receive our emails please contact us immediately at customerservice@funkluscious.com to be removed for our list.
Utilisez votre liste de contrôle pour procéder à votre petite campagne de marketing électronique de l’entreprise e, personnellement pour moi le résultat du traitement par le Vardenafil acheté ici est super. Un chirurgien canadien regorgeant de technologie bon marché et de flux d’achats en ligne Xenical. Quand j’ai été trop surpris et plus surpris quand il est accepté par le livre et je n’ai pas à l’utiliser comme un sort pilule bleue, je ne conseille pas d’acheter du Levitra 2. Il croit que les performances d’improvisation aident les gens à atteindre un niveau supérieur, urination pendant l’estomac ou la poitrine hématurie. Le Cialis Original est l’un des meilleurs médicaments contre la dysfonction érectile, placez le siège enfant dans un bain-marie frais et normal.
Home
About
Personalization
Holiday & Celebrations
Wedding & Marriage
Accessories
Everything Else!
Item Added to your Cart!
There are no products
Continue Shopping
